Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- CSEA Publications, 1932-2014; 5; 15.04 cubic ft. 2686 Digital Files
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 November 7 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 November 14 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 November 21 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 November 28 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 December 5 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 December 12 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 December 19 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1961 December 26 (Reel 8)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 January 2 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 January 9 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 January 16 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 January 23 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 January 30 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 February 6 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 February 13 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 February 20 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 February 27 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 March 6 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 March 13 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 March 20 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 March 27 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 April 3 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 April 10 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 April 17 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 April 24 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 May 1 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 May 8 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 May 15 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 May 22 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 May 29 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 June 5 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 June 12 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 June 19 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 June 26 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 July 3 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 July 10 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 July 17 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 July 24 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 July 31 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 August 7 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 August 14 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 August 21 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 August 28 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 September 4 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 September 11 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 September 18 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 September 25 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 October 2 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 October 9 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 October 16 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 October 23 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 October 30 (Reel 9)
  - The Wineless Vine, Official Grapevine-Suffolk Chapter, CSEA, 1962 October (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 November 6 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 November 6 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 November 13 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 November 20 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 November 27 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 December 4 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 December 11 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 December 18 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1962 December 25 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 January 1 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 January 8 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 January 15 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 January 22 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 January 29 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 February 5 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 February 12 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 February 19 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 February 26 (Reel 9)
  - Weekly Newsletter of the Civil Service Employees Association, 1963 February (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 March 5 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 March 12 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 March 19 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 March 26 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 April 2 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 April 9 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 April 16 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 April 23 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 April 30 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 May 7 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 May 14 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 May 21 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 May 28 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 June 4 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 June 11 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 June 18 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 June 25 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 July 2 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 July 9 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 July 16 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 July 23 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 July 30 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 August 6 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 August 13 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 August 20 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 August 27 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 September 3 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 September 10 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 September 17 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 September 24 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 October 1 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 October 8 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 October 15 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 October 22 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 October 29 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 November 5 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 November 12 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 November 19 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 November 26 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 December 3 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 December 10 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 December 17 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 December 24 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1963 December 31 (Reel 9)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 January 7 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 January 14 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 January 21 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 January 28 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 February 4 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 February 11 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 February 18 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 February 25 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 March 3 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 March 10 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 March 17 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 March 24 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 March 31 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 April 7 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 April 14 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 April 21 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 April 28 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 May 5 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 May 12 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 May 19 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 May 26 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 June 2 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 June 9 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 June 16 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 June 23 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 June 30 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 July 7 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 July 14 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 July 21 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 July 28 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 August 4 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 August 11 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 August 18 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 August 25 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 September 1 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 September 8 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 September 15 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 September 22 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 September 29 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 October 6 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 October 13 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 October 20 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 October 27 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 November 3 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 November 10 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 November 17 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 November 24 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 December 1 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 December 8 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 December 15 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 December 22 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1964 December 29 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 January 5 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 January 12 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 January 19 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 January 26 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 February 2 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 February 9 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 February 16 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 February 23 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 March 2 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 March 9 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 March 16 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 March 23 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 March 30 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 April 6 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 April 13 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 April 20 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 April 27 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 May 4 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 May 11 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 May 18 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 May 25 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 June 1 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 June 8 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 June 15 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 June 22 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 June 29 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 July 6 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 July 13 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 July 20 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 July 27 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 August 3 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 August 10 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 August 17 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 August 24 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 August 31 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 September 7 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 September 14 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 September 21 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 September 28 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 October 5 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 October 12 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 October 19 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 October 26 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 November 2 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 November 9 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 November 16 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 November 23 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 November 30 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 December 7 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 December 14 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 December 21 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1965 December 28 (Reel 10)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 January 4 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 January 11 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 January 18 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 January 25 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 February 1 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 February 8 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 February 15 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 February 22 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 March 1 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 March 8 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 March 15 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 March 22 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 March 29 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 April 5 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 April 12 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 April 19 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 April 26 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 May 3 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 May 10 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 May 17 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 May 24 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 May 31 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 June 7 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 June 14 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 June 21 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 June 28 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 July 5 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 July 12 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 July 19 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 July 26 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 August 2 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 August 9 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 August 16 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 August 23 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 August 30 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 September 6 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 September 13 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 September 20 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 September 26 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 September 27 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 October 4 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 October 11 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 October 18 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 October 25 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 November 1 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 November 8 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 November 15 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 November 22 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 November 29 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 December 6 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 December 13 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 December 20 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1966 December 27 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 January 3 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 January 10 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 January 17 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 January 24 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 January 31 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 February 7 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 February 14 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 February 21 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 February 28 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 March 7 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 March 14 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 March 21 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 March 28 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 April 4 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 April 11 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 April 18 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 April 25 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 May 2 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 May 9 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 May 16 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 May 23 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 May 30 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 June 6 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 June 13 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 June 20 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 June 27 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 July 4 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 July 11 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 July 18 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 July 25 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 August 1 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 August 8 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 August 15 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 August 22 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 August 29 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 September 5 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 September 12 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 September 19 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 September 26 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 October 2 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 October 3 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 October 10 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 October 17 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 October 24 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 October 31 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 November 7 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 November 14 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 November 21 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 November 28 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 December 5 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 December 12 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 December 19 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1967 December 26 (Reel 11)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 January 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 January 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 January 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 January 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 January 30
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 February 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 February 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 February 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 February 27
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 March 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 March 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 March 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 March 26
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 April 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 April 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 April 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 April 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 April 30
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 May 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 May 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 May 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 May 28
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 June 4
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 June 11
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 June 18
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 June 25
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 July 2
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 July 9
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 July 16
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 July 23
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 July 30
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 August 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 August 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 August 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 August 27
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 September 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 October 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 October 29
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 November 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 November 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 November 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 November 26
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 December 3
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 December 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 December 17
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 December 24
  - Civil Service Leader, 1968 December 31
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 January 7
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 January 14
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 January 21
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 January 28
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 February 4
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 February 11
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 February 18
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 February 25
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 March 4
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 March 11
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 March 18
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 March 25
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 April 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 April 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 April 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 April 22
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 April 29
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 May 6
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 May 13
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 May 20
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 May 27
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 June 3
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 June 10
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 June 17
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 June 24
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 July 1
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 July 8
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 July 15
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 July 22
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 July 29
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 August 5
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 August 12
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 August 19
  - Civil Service Leader, 1969 August 26
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 January 6 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 January 13 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 January 20 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 January 27 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 February 3 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 February 10 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 February 17 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 February 24 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 March 3 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 March 10 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 March 17 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 March 24 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 March 31 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 April 7 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 April 14 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 April 21 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 April 28 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 May 5 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 May 12 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 May 19 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 May 26 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 June 2 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 June 9 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 June 16 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 June 23 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 June 30 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 July 7 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 July 14 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 July 21 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 July 28 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 August 4 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 August 11 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 August 18 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 August 25 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 September 1 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 September 8 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 September 15 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 September 22 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 September 29 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 October 3 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 October 6 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 October 13 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 October 20 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 October 27 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 November 10 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 November 17 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 November 24 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 December 1 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 December 8 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 December 15 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 December 22 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1970 December 29 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 January 5 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 January 12 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 January 19 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 January 26 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 February 2 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 February 9 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 February 16 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 February 23 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 March 2 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 March 9 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 March 16 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 March 23 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 March 30 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 April 6 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 April 13 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 April 20 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 April 27 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 May 4 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 May 11 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 May 18 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 May 25 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 June 1 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 June 8 (Reel 12)
  - Civil Service Leader, 1971 June 15 (Reel 12)